Okay hello everyone welcome to Indian stock
market so gas today we will talk
about stop tips but before that please
subscribe to my channel like
comment share and do
n't forget to press the bell icon your love and
support if you do like this so let's
learn something new today so gas today we will talk
about stock tips first let's talk about
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company the
fundamentals of the company are strong the
financials of the company are quite strong
you have to buy a short term delivery
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company NSC -
0.90% with the target price of 1471 the
current market price of ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company Limited is
10161.8
ok the target is 1470 you have to buy a short term
delivery current market
price
₹161 with the target price of Rs 1470
General Insurance Company Limited in
Corporation
33 crore operating in financial services
sector is a finance company ICICI
Lombard General Insurance Company Limited
ok this product revenue segment
including  Miscellaneous Insurance Other
Operating Revenue Fire Insurance
for D Year Ending 31st March 2022 OK
Financials
30th September
Total Income of
₹4741 crore now up
13.38% from last quarter Total Income of
38 crore
18.4% from last year to quarter Total
Income of
3982.273 crore in latest quarter
OK So Gas Promoters Phir Holdings
Promoter Health
48.03% Strike in D Company As of 30th June
2022fri on
26.434% OK OK
So Gas ICICI Lombard General
Insurance Company from - 0.90% with D
Target Price
1470 The current market price of
ICICI Lombard General Insurance
Company Limited 1161
is the target of 1470 is a short term delivery
you have to buy the fundamentals of the company
Piston of the company financials are somewhat
strong OK So Gas That's all for today, see you
tomorrow, till then allow me to say
namaskar  Say Radhe Radhe